Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hello!
Help!
Anyone?
Fuck! Okay. Okay. okay.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right. who are you?
What am I doing here?
And why did you hit me in the head?
Did we need that?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Are you French?
Someone is coming to talk to you.
Who is? Who's coming to talk to me?
Fuck. Okay. Yeah.
Who's coming to talk to me?
Did you take my phone?
Did you-- Wait. wait!
Can you-- Fucking.
Merde!
Shit.
David. here's another cup of tea.
Well. I hope this one's strong enough.
Charles used to like his tea so weak
I used to say.
"Do you want some tea with your milk?"
Do you remember Charles?
David?
I killed him.
- River.
- No.
No. that was someone
who looked like him. Remember?
Someone who looked like him?
Dear God. what have I done?
David. that was self-defense.
No. I did it for River.
To protect him. To protect River.
Where is he?
Where's my boy?
Why did he leave me here?
David?
Who are you?
I'm Catherine Standish.
I used to work with River.
And. before that.
I worked for Charles Partner.
No. No. I don't remember you.
You knew Charles. you say?
- Yes. I was his PA.
- I--
And then I was Jackson's PA.
The bomb.
All those people.
- All those poor people.
- No. David. The bomb wasn't you.
David.
- I must speak to First Desk.
- You can't go to the Park.
- River doesn't want that.
- No.
- Get your hands off me.
- No. David.
- Don't touch me!
- I'm sorry.
I have to talk to First Desk.
I have to tell them what happened.
- What's coming.
- What's coming?
What happened?
The bomb.
River.
I have--
Why am I talking to you?
I remember you.
You're just a bloody secretary.
- Get me First Desk.
- David. David. listen.
Listen. First Desk is very busy. Yes?
- I mean. you know what it's like.
- No.
They'll talk to me.
I used to run the damn place.
I know you did.
But at this time of day. he'll be
reading the cables from Berlin. won't he?
Berlin? Oh. yes. Yes. of course. That--
- And he--
- The schedule.
That's right.
And he's got to get that right.
I mean. agents in play.
awaiting instructions.
We can't interrupt that.
No. no. It's very dangerous.
So. if you will allow me.
I will call the Park right now.
and I will get you the first
available appointment after that.
You can do that?
I'm a secretary. That's what I do.
Here. sit.
Okay.
- Yeah.
- Here's your tea.
Thank you.
I'll be back in a minute.
- It's very kind of you.
- You're welcome.
I need to speak to First Desk.
Yes.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
Who's upstairs?
The usual bunch of dead weights.
Shit rises to the top in this building
with the gold at the bottom.
Although. you have the top office.
so I'll take that back.
Listen. you tit. in the last hour.
someone walked up those stairs
in shoes that are outside your salary.
Who?
Well. it's not my fault.
I didn't know who she was.
And if I'd had known.
I couldn't have stopped her.
Were you here when she came in?
No. that's not my fault.
Is River headed to Lavande?
Go to Catherine's.
get her to move David Cartwright.
David's with Catherine?
What about River?
Well. this wasn't in the diary.
Lucky I have a free slot.
Has anyone offered you tea or coffee?
- No.
- Yeah. well. it's just as well.
I think there's
something dead in the water tank.
So. how can I help?
I think you know why I'm here.
You've not been relegated
to Slough House already. have you?
What the fuck did you do?
Get caught drinking on the job?
You can drop the act.
I know you're
not the shambling fool you appear.
Blood work come back. has it?
Well. what can I say?
He's my joe.
He wanted everyone to think he was dead.
and I helped keep it that way
for as long as I could.
He might be your joe. but he's MI5's agent
and he was present at a murder scene.
Maybe he even pulled the trigger.
I'm bringing him in.
Well. be my guest.
I don't know where the fuck he is.
So. you can put the thumbscrews on me.
'cause that's the only
answer you're gonna get.
I'm taking you in for
obstructing an investigation. Get up.
Nah. I'm good here. thanks.
I got a full day
of fuck all to get through.
Well. the carload of Dogs
I'm about to call
might get in the way of that.
Well. I wouldn't want people to think
they had to send a bunch of men
to do a woman's job.
Now. cuffs won't be necessary. Come on.
I'd rather not take any chances with a man
who looks like he gropes people on buses.
You're being hurtful about my appearance.
I might have to call HR.
Look. I get why you're angry.
You would have told Taverner
that River was dead.
and she did a little jig
and now you gotta go back and tell her
that the most troublesome agent
is alive and well
and in the wind doing fuck knows what.
So. by way of amends.
I'm happy to give you David Cartwright.
Why would you do that?
Because going to the Park
is like being in IKEA.
You can never get
out of the fucking place.
Go on then.
Do I look like an idiot?
You know. talking about your looks
could get me into all sorts of trouble.
You'd burn David Cartwright to avoid
being taken in yourself?
River's my joe.
But Cartwright's a piece of shit.
The idea of him sitting in a basement cell
stirs my nethers.
Where is he?
Hey.
Hey. apologies.
What for?
Well. I didn't realize you were a Dog.
I mean. obviously you're not a dog.
Where did you park your wings?
Meaning you're an angel.
In case you thought I was implying
you were a seagull or a crow.
But with those legs.
you're more of a flamingo. aren't ya?
Hey!
Well. I've actually got
a girlfriend anyway. so you lose.
I can just slip this off. so...
double lose.
- Hi.
Giti? Is it Giti?
- Is it Giti? It is.
- Yeah.
No. please. Please. sit down.
Sit down. No hierarchy here.
All is one. I like to think to myself.
It's just Diana Taverner
commended you to me for your--
The work you did on the cold body case.
And I wanted to say thank you very much.
Thank you. Such a relief it was a glitch.
Yes. Yes. it was. Yeah.
Gave us all
a bit of a scare though for a minute.
I didn't mean
to cause any unnecessary panic.
Oh. no. no. Totally necessary.
I mean.
we've got to explore every possibility.
And in fact. that actually got me
to thinking. because
I thought it would be a very good idea
to double-check the archives
for any other glitches. you know.
Anomalies in the cold body program.
Okay.
I did actually suggest that to her.
- Second Desk.
- Did you?
And she said I'd be better placed
on current duties.
Did she? Yeah.
Well. she's absolutely right. of course.
From her perspective.
I mean. she's running live ops. isn't she?
And with Westacres ongoing.
she doesn't have the bandwidth
for this kind of. what should we say.
speculative investigation.
But I do and I would like you
to report direct to me.
I'd love to.
- Love is probably the wrong word.
- Yeah. probably.
- It will be okay with her. won't it?
- Yeah. that's a bit--
I don't want to get in any trouble.
No. no. no. keep this between ourselves.
I think.
Discretion being the better part of valor.
And you'll be getting us ahead
of any potential trouble.
which would be a big help in fact.
So if there's anything
that I can do to facilitate that.
please do tell me.
Please. after you.
- Have you been in here before?
- I haven't.
- Have you met Molly?
- No.
A lot of fun. A lot of fun.
- Hello. Molly.
- Hello. Weasel.
Weasel's a term they use
to refer to those of us
that use gaming programs
to refine long-term strategy.
That's actually what that means.
You'll always be a Weasel to me.
Yeah. Molly. I'm First Desk. all right?
Not appropriate. is it?
- So. cold bodies?
- Yes.
Yes. Giti here thinks that she may
have found one connected to Westacres.
So. what I'd like her to do is to
double-check that there aren't
any of our old cold bodies
out there in the world being used.
You understand?
If you wouldn't mind
affording her the run of this place.
facilitating in any way that you can.
I'd appreciate that.
Thank you.
Thank you so much. Giti. Thank you.
I've had enough of games
between First and Second Desk.
Yeah. me too. Well. it's funny.
It's funny. because who do you think
comes first in that?
You know. when I say First Desk and
then I say Second Desk. who do you think--
Diana Taverner.
Natasha!
Who are you?
Are you the person
who's been wanting to talk to me?
We're the ones with the gun.
So. we ask the questions here.
Okay.
You look like someone from Les Arbres.
You have a passport with his photo in.
and you're not him.
What were you doing there?
I'm guessing from the fact
that he keeps pointing that at me
that you didn't like this guy very much.
So. maybe
he'll put it down when I tell you
that he can't hurt anyone anymore
because he's dead.
Why is he not putting the gun down?
He was my son.
How did he die?
He turned up at my grandfather's
pretending to be me
because he was going
to drown him in a bath.
But then my grandfather shot him.
It was bound to end that way.
With a father like that.
Look. right.
I'm MI5. Okay?
The British security service.
We don't care.
You-- Just go.
Yes.
Look. look.
I'm sorry about your son.
but I need to know who he was.
You've been asking to leave. now leave.
You really need to stop
pointing that at me. Okay?
Who are they?
They think you are Bertrand.
Right. But I'm not Bertrand. am I?
Can you tell them that?
- Tell them yourself.
- I'm-- All right. look.
Listen to me. all right?
You see this? You see this man?
The one next to your son?
- Yeah.
- He was at Les Arbres too. right?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well. you know the bomb in London?
The one at the shops?
That was him.
He set that off.
And that could happen again.
So. you need to tell me
who these people are
and where I can find them.
Catherine. it's Louisa. Again.
Emma Flyte. new head Dog.
is on her way to you.
She's after David Cartwright.
You need to get him out before she--
Oh. shit.
Excuse me?
Excuse me? Hi.
I'm really sorry.
but I think someone's following me.
Do you think you could just walk
with me to the end of the road?
I can't see anyone.
They're probably hiding.
I just-- I was in the shop earlier
and I came back out.
and I thought he had disappeared.
but then he was right behind me again.
Not him. is it?
No. This guy is just-- He's much younger.
He's got really scary eyes.
and he's just really dangerous.
Okay. Well. you're in luck.
'cause I'm with the security services.
Thank God. Can we walk?
- My colleague will deal with it.
- Okay.
- Great. Thank you.
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I was just speaking to your colleague.
I thought someone was following me.
but they're not.
- So. it's all--
- You sure?
- Yeah. Thank you. Fuck's sake.
- You look familiar.
Wow. Vulnerable woman
and you're trying it on?
No. God. no. No.
I just feel like we've met. That is all.
Right. You just stop right there
before I report you.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
So now you're following me?
Just tryna help. man.
Emma Flyte. Head of security for the Park.
Can I see some ID. please?
- How can I help?
- You can let me inside.
Do you have a warrant?
You're still a member of the service.
which means
you're subject to my jurisdiction.
Which means I don't need a warrant.
Except I resigned a while ago.
Yes. Not exactly.
You handed in your resignation.
but the paperwork seems to have stalled.
Remind me.
are you still receiving a salary?
Receiving. not spending.
Doesn't matter.
You're on the books. so open up.
...updates on the progress
of the Westacres investigation
is the Deputy Commissioner...
Still keeping a hand in. I see.
I'm allowed to keep up with the news.
- Nice flat.
- Thank you.
Quiet area too.
And you're a reader.
Nothing spoils a good book
faster than a lot of background noise.
Unless it's unwelcome visitors.
- Talking of visitors. where is he?
- Who?
David Cartwright.
Dav-- I haven't seen
David Cartwright in over 20 years. so--
Please don't go in there.
Why would he--
I asked you not to come in here.
I don't like strangers in my bedroom.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. but are we in some sort of
West End farce?
Oh. for God's sake.
Why is this locked?
It's not. It's just stiff.
You have to open it gently
or that happens. See?
I've probably put too much in here.
Look. who told you he was here?
Jackson Lamb.
Oh. well. he'll have sent you here
purely to distress me.
We've had a falling out.
I'm afraid you've been used. Miss Flyte.
Just a moment.
Good luck with finding David.
You should try asking his grandson. River.
where he is.
All right. Back in a bit.
You know. it might be an idea
to hold on to that gun.
Everyone's a target.
Post-Westacres. we don't know where
or when the next attack will come.
Put your headphones in.
and shut the fuck up.
It's bad karma to sell it.
It's bad karma to have
the Christmas decorations still up.
Weapons on the street versus
tinsel-based superstition.
Yeah. exactly the same.
Look. I don't want to be doing this.
but I've got no choice.
Cassie's already noticing
the unpaid bills.
- It's a fucking nightmare.
- Of your own creation.
Look. I sort this. and I'm done.
For real this time.
Hi. Can you come down and help me?
Fuck off.
Ho wants help.
Unless it's with assisting his suicide.
I'm not interested.
Look. I'm handcuffed
to my weights machine.
He's handcuffed to his weight machine.
Worth a look.
Was this an accident
or part of a wanking game?
It was Flyte.
Good on her.
I'm not gonna bother asking why.
'cause I'm sure it was deserved.
Look. are you gonna help me?
No.
What are you doing?
I mean. at least leave him there overnight
or till he shits himself.
I have to help him.
No. you don't.
Do you want to know why
I'm going to free him?
I want to know why
you're holding a knife to my throat.
Well. before I was assigned here.
I was handcuffed against my will
and tied to a chair for 72 hours.
So. I find him being cuffed triggering.
Okay. Got it.
What happened while you were handcuffed?
A man threatened to cut open my stomach.
He had an electric...
carving knife.
Badarse.
Brothers in cuffs.
I don't like to be touched.
What the fuck.
Victor is my cousin.
Is he?
Nice to meet you. Victor.
He was the only one who stood by me
when I was made pregnant by
the man at Les Arbres.
I was 17.
And that's this man?
Yes.
Frank Harkness.
Although. he told so many lies.
that may not be his real name.
Well. he never let me see my son.
So. I moved away and I would come
back sometimes to see Bertrand.
and he looked through me
like I didn't exist.
We heard everyone at Les Arbres was gone.
and she would never see Bertrand again.
I thought you were him.
So. I called her. followed you.
Found Frank trying to kill you.
And then you hit me...
Why would Frank try to kill you?
Well. I think he was destroying evidence.
and I just got in his way.
And the bomber. what about him?
- Yves.
Well. that's no surprise.
The way he was treated as a boy.
You could see his hate. his anger.
So. you lived at Les Arbres?
Yeah.
While Bertrand was little.
Did you paint this?
No. One of the other girls did.
Other girls?
Yes. The mothers.
You know. there were some Russians.
a Greek.
Maybe an English
and another local girl. I think.
They have his children.
and then he makes the mothers leave
because that's--
that's how he wants things to be.
I'll speak to them.
Tell them you are not
who they think you are.
Yeah. please.
Wow. They really didn't like your son.
did they?
Well. the man out there.
Bertrand put his son in the hospital
and assaulted his daughter.
So. we don't really blame him
for his hate.
Victor will calm them.
- Fuck me. Jesus.
- Run.
That's a big dog.
It's not him!
It's not Bertrand!
Shit.
Come on.
Monsieur.
All right. fuck off!
What the fucking--
Why aren't you answering your phone?
- How have you been. by the way?
- River has it. And I'm fine. Thank you.
Why didn't Lamb just tell me that?
So. Lamb sent you?
Yeah. Where's David?
Luckily I moved him.
It took Lamb all of five minutes
to work out how to find him.
I mean. he's smarter than most.
but he's not the only brain
on Spook Street.
David thinks he's meeting
First Desk in a safe house.
- Where?
- Number 25.
I'm cat-sitting for my neighbor.
So. how was River when you saw him?
He's all right considering.
He's not answering your phone.
He won't do. He's taken out the SIM card.
I'm sorry Lamb told you River was dead.
That must have been very hard.
Yeah. it's pretty much the final straw.
I might join you on the outside.
You'd get very bored.
What's the Westacres news?
Nothing.
Although they're not
ruling out further attacks.
Any idea who tried to kill David?
Just that they came from France.
Hello. Pinkel.
Are you allergic to cats?
No. I just don't really like them.
David?
Catherine!
The back door's open!
Oh. my God.
Oh. fuck.
What am I going to tell River?
What am I gonna tell Lamb?
...will I be free.
You will suffer for the years
I spent imprisoned by your system.
God willing. I will not be the last.
You will hear from my brothers soon.
I'm here on the...
...just outside of
the Westacres Shopping Center.
where the mood is still...
I'm afraid I've got some bad news.
What the fuck's that?
This? It's just a simple tussie-mussie.
Fuck off.
It's a nosegay.
People used to sniff them
during the great plague
to cancel out the stench of death.
Fuck off.
I've asked my contacts back at the Park.
and there isn't a single shred of evidence
that David Cartwright ever went to France.
So. I suppose our deal is off.
I'm afraid so.
Looks like I'm stuck with you.
I did discover that his bagman went there
in the early 90s.
Lavande?
Yes.
Go see Ho. and tell him I said
to find out why you're at Slough House.
- Really?
- Well. yeah.
Yeah. I don't want you here.
And letting me know that Bad Sam Chapman
went to France is good enough.
Here you are. Take a closer look.
Sure you haven't seen him?
He lives right across from here.
Thirteen. Looks a bit older.
Goes by the name of KZ.
Do you mean KayZee?
You know him then?
Depends. is there money in it?
Well. there could be.
How about an advance then?
I don't have any cash on me.
And you know. I don't think
you've got anything to tell me.
Well. we can walk you to a cashpoint.
I'm ugly enough I don't mind
getting hit in the face. How about you?
Paedo.
Hello. trouble.
I need a meet.
Launderette number three.
What if I've got
something more important to do?
You don't.
I have eyes on the old man.
Okay. so take him out.
He's in public now.
Let him know he's being followed.
He'll get nervous. try and hide.
Kill him out of sight.
then move on to Cartwright.
Dancer Blaine?
Got a bit of merchandise for you.
Who sent you?
No one.
How do you know about me?
I'm MI5.
Is this a sting?
Not much of a sting if I tell you
I'm MI5 from the off. right?
Fair point.
All right.
Do you know why they call me Dancer?
'Cause you're into ballroom dancing?
And also because I sense danger
and dance right around it.
Now. serving MI5 officer.
well. that screams trouble to me.
Why do you want to sell me a gun?
- I need money. right and fast.
- So. rob a bank.
If you don't want the gun.
fine by me. I'll take it elsewhere.
No. you won't. You need the cash.
That's the other thing
about being a dancer.
You learn to read people.
Anticipate their moves.
And I can tell you've got a good heart.
But you're all out of moves.
Beretta M9.
Beat out the Sig Sauer P226
to become the primary sidearm
of the US Army from 1985 to present.
- Three grand.
- It's worth five.
Yeah. No. I can sell it for five.
That's how profit works.
- All right. four and a half.
- Three.
- Four.
- Three and a half.
- Three.
- Perfect.
Great negotiating.
Any time this year would be great.
Picked up a tail.
Where are you?
Leading them away from you.
Could be a case I'm working
looking for a 13-year-old.
Runaway.
Got mixed up with the wrong crowd.
Just faced some of them down.
- Could be them.
- It's not.
Someone tried to whack
David Cartwright last night.
Shit. Who?
I don't know. but the old bastard
blew him away with a shotgun.
- Anyone come looking for you?
- Not yet.
I'll head to fallback number two.
I'll have the Slow Horses follow you
from the market
in case your tail makes a move.
Nice of you to call me back.
Lamb called. He needs us as a backup
for a meet with Bad Sam Chapman.
He said to tail him from the market
to fallback number two.
Yeah. that's the old garage.
Actually. I'm not far.
All right. be there soon as.
Make sure you come packing heat.
Oh. no. You can't.
Shut up.
Shirley!
Fucking hell.
Do you wanna draw any more attention?
Chapman's 200 yards ahead.
All right. Where's the tail?
I thought I saw him. but he's disappeared.
Probably saw me coming and scarpered.
I mean. that hat would do it.
Shit.
- Are you all right?
- No.
Fucking hell.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
Fuck.
Come on. come on. come on.
I can't seem to shake him.
- Abort.
- No. keep moving.
- I'll be there.
- Okay.
Come out. old man.
It's over. Let's go.
You all right?
Here. get him up and in the cab.
I'll deal with the roadkill.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-